const people =  [{"id":350,"question":"Normalizations is...","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"concerned with the physical implementation of the database","answer_b":"a database design technique that encourages storing data in multiple databases","answer_c":"a database design technique that eliminates relationships from a database","answer_d":"a database design technique used to minimize data redundancy and duplication","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":420,"question":"What Is a MySQL View?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"VIEWS are virtual tables that do not store any data of their own but display data stored in other tables.","answer_b":"VIEWS are static tables that store data but the data can't be changed","answer_c":"VIEWS are temporary tables that store data which store data only for a certain amount of time","answer_d":"VIEWS are no different that any other tables except they are used for faster loading.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":355,"question":"The command DROP SCHEMA `STUDENTS`; will delete the students database.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":422,"question":"Is the NULL value treated as 0?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":368,"question":"MySQL supports user defined functions","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":394,"question":"To use MySQL on your computer, you'll need","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Perl, PHP Or Java","answer_b":"FTP And Telnet","answer_c":"Some Sort Of Client Program To Access The Databases","answer_d":"A Browser","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":369,"question":"Which of the following is a valid aggregate function","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CURDATE()","answer_b":"COUNT","answer_c":"AVERAGE","answer_d":"MAXIMUM","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":389,"question":"The maximum length of the char columns is","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"65, 535 Bytes","answer_b":"None Of The Mentioned","answer_c":"255 Bytes","answer_d":"256 Bytes","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":217,"question":"What is the use of SQL?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Storing data in database","answer_b":"Manipulating data in database","answer_c":"Retrieving data in database","answer_d":"Displaying images","answer_e":"Managing queries","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":425,"question":"TCL is used for _______?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Control access to data stored in a database","answer_b":"Managing the changes made by DML statements","answer_c":"Defining database schema","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"}]
export default people;